## Mitchell Drew Fernandez

070-8321-3033 Kamishinjo Station mitchellfernandez147@gmail.com



### **Profile**

My name is Mitchell Fernandez, Im a 26 year old Australian living in Higashiyodogawaku, Osaka-Shi, Japan. I am currently looking for full time or part time employment in Nagano prefecture as my wife and I wish to move there. I am living here on a Spousal Visa and I am eligible to work in Japan. I am a great people person and a devoted worker. I hope you will consider me for a position with you.

# Experience

#### **ENGLISH TEACHER, SIEHA ENGLISH ACADEMY, OSAKA - 01/2020**

This role is as an English Teacher at Seiha English Academy is Osaka. Seiha is a Eikaiwa with multiple schools all over the country. I have been based in the Osaka area working at multiple schools and teaching students of all different levels and ages. I teach students aged from 0 to 15 years of age with the occasional adult classes. This job has been greatly rewarding and enjoyable, my only reason for leaving is too look for work in Nagano as my wife and I wish to move there. In this role I would teach everything from basic english with songs, dances and games to teaching grammar and writing to older students. I love working with my students and watching them improve everyday. I have been quite successful in my teaching methods and often have my trial students sign up to be taught by me. This position has taught me a lot about teaching but I am hoping I can keep improving my skills further in a new position.

ASSISTANT ENGLISH TEACHER, FOREST INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL, OSAKA - 04/2019 - 11/2019

This role is as an English Assistant Teacher at an International pre school in Osaka-Shi. This role is my first role working with Children in Japan. I work with a class of students aged 1 to 3 years old. This role entails but is not limited to: assisting students during class and lessons, helping students during lunch and snack times, accompanying students in the bathroom and assisting them, teaching lessons, reading stories too students, ensuring the safety of the students at all times.

### MEMBER SERVICE OFFICER, HERITAGE BANK, TOOWOOMBA, QLD - 12/2018 - 02/2019

This job was based in the Heritage Bank call centre in their head office, some of my day to day tasks included but are not limited to: Answering phone calls from people of many different cultural backgrounds, Giving customers financial services and advice, Customer Service, Assisting customers with online and telephone banking, processing customers financial information - Term deposits - insurance sales - home loan sales.

#### STORE MANAGER, HUSKY GAS STATION, LAKE LOUISE, ALBERTA - 02/2018 - 10/2018

This role as a Store Manager of a gas station and convenience store some of my day to day tasks included but are not limited to: Cash handling and use of cashier register,

Scheduling staff, Product order and inventory, Stock management, Training of new employees, Maintenance of store and facilities.

CUSTOMER SERVICE OFFICER, DEPARTMENT OF HUMAN SERVICES, TOOWOOMBA, QLD – 2014 - 2017

This was a role in a call centre for the Australian Federal Governments Welfare Department: Centrelink. Some of my day to day tasks included but were not limited to: Inbound calls from the Australian public, Dealing with Sensitive matters, High processing and data entry, updating customer information, Deciding outcomes on customer claims, Online help desk support, consulting with Social workers, Assessment of finances, Speaking with customers from many different backgrounds and nationalities, Assisting elderly Australians with there pensions and Residential Care Assessments.

#### SALES REPRESENTATIVE, AIDA/FOXTEL - 2013 - 2014

This was a role in sales as a door to door salesman. Some of my day to day tasks included but were not limited to: Product training, Face to face sales, Recruitment/training of new staff, Data entry and paperwork, Managing a client database.

### Education

Harristown State High School, Toowoomba, QLD - Graduated 2012 - Year 12 CertificateCertificate II in Hospitality - 2012 Responsible Service of Alcohol - 2012 Responsible Service in Gambling - 2012

## Skills

Punctual, Resourceful, Friendly, Very quick learner, Adaptable to any environment, Critical thinker and problem solver, Great IT and computer skills, Efficient in Microsoft programs, Efficient with computer hardware, Management skills, Able to work well with others, Knowledge of computer software, Outstanding customer service skills, Ability to converse with people from many backgrounds and nationalities also younger and older people, Word processing, Great phone manner, Polite, Reliable and efficient worker. I also have experience teaching English in Japan.

### References

Arthur Lee - Seiha English Academy - Osaka North Area Manager

Phone: 090-1328-9184 Email: <u>arthur\_lee@seiha.com</u>

Relationship: Manager

Yukiko Hayashi - Seiha English Academy - Osaka North JT Sub-Manager

Phone: 090-1153-1437

Email: <a href="mailto:yukiko\_hayashi@seiha.com">yukiko\_hayashi@seiha.com</a></a><br/>Relationship: Co-Teacher and Manager

Cherie Achilles - Department of Human Services - Team Leader

Phone: 0746132580

Email: <a href="mailto:cherie.achilles@humanservices.gov.au">cherie.achilles@humanservices.gov.au</a>

Relationship: Team Leader

Sooz Osborn - Department of Human Services - Team Leader

Phone: 0746132753

Email: sooz.osborn@humanservices.gov.au

Relationship: Team Leader